妖女前情提要
Previously on Lost Girl...
你是流浪者吗
Are you The Wanderer?
我知道你会为我回来的
I knew you'd come for me.
我记起流浪者是谁了
I remember who The Wanderer is.
这一切都是我造成的
I created all of this.
我必须带走他的灵魂
I must take his soul.
它是属于我的
It belongs to me.
你们还看不出这是怎么回事
Don't you see what is happening to me?
一无所知快把我搞疯了
Not knowing is driving me crazy.
你深爱的某人很快就会死去
Someone you love very much will soon be dead.
我这样做因为他并非我的敌人
I did all of this because he's not my enemy,
他是我的命中注定
he's my destiny.
你刚说命中注定
Did you just say destiny?!
你有什么事都冲我来
If you have something to settle, settle it with me.
放过我的外孙女
Not my granddaughter.
你没听见我刚才说什么了吗
Did you not hear what I just said?
你被他洗脑了
He's brainwashed you!
你们就不能相信我一下吗
Can you please trust me, any of you?
到底发生了什么事
What is going on?
我来搞定，Bo，你回来
I'll take care of this. Bo, get back!
你才给我滚回去 你们都是
No you need to get back. All of you.
开弓没有回头箭 我们没得选择
It had to be done,they didn't give us a choice.
我一周工作90个小时
I have been pulling ninety-hour weeks
就为了这个牛逼指数赶超苹果的手机发布
to make this the biggest mobile launch since the iPhone.
你们这帮常春藤傻逼再给老子拖延
One more delay from you or any of your Ivy League morons
Darren就把你们给五马分尸
and Darren will have you sliced in two.
很好
Good.
你可真乖
You're a doll.
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
Ah...aaaaahhhhhh!
本作品片源来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作学习交流之用
任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途
挪威金毛的胡须最有爱了字幕组  r(st)q
英文字幕：来自互联网
翻译：Neffititi 骷髅头正宫_K
精校：Momo酱各种大爱 潜行的五
压制：Neffititi
发布：百度贴吧Tamsin后援群
资源下载请关注瓦尔基里字幕组官方微博
4x10 Waves
我们根本不该让她独自回那列火车上
We should never have let her get on that train alone.
我们应该保护她的
We should have protected her.
可她不需要我们的保护，Dyson
She doesn't want our protection Dyson,
她连见一见我们都不肯了
she doesn't even want to see us.
她脑子糊涂了
She's not thinking straight.
肯定是被什么附身了，要不就是啥魔咒
It's got to be a possession.Or a spell.
我需要给她做个检查
I just...I need to examine her.
这就对了，我去叫她
That's it,I'm gonna go get her.
但她不让我们检查她啊，Dyson
But she doesn't want us to Dyson.
我不管
I don't care.
Dyson，她把我们排除在外了
Dyson she locked us out.
Bo把我们排除在外了
Bo locked us out.
原来我们在砸东西啊
Aaaaaand we're breaking things.
大杯咖啡，你们来拿呀，来呀
Giant coffees! Come and get 'em!
谁会需要辣么多咖啡因啊
Who could possibly need that much caffeine?
我们，咱们，我们要破案了，来点掌声好吗
Us! We! We're taking a case. Can I get a wha' wha'.
啥
What?
什么
好吧，和我想的不太一样
Okay,not what I had in mind.
Kenzi 现在不是说这的时候
Kenzi,it's not really a good time.
一个女人的腿没了同志们，就酱紫没了好么
A woman's legs went missing, dudes! Like mi-ssing. Okay?
她在公司的游泳池游泳，忽然咔嚓一声
She was swimming in her company pool, and then BAM.
在池子里腿没了
Legless in Pool-attle.
那公司叫啥名字
What's the company called?
Alaria科技，搞生物识别技术的
Alaria Tech. Biometrics.
<机械公敌>里的那种，我们得深挖到底
Like "I, Robot" shit. So we need to get to the bottom of this.
*I,Robot 著名科幻作品 曾被多次改编为电影及电视剧 机器人三定律即出自此作*
还要把底下那一半给拿回来
And, get that bottom half...back.
可我们现在唯一的案子应该是Bo，肯子
Yeah, Bo's kind of our only case right now Kenz.
好吧但是Bo已经说得很清楚了
Yeah,well Bo's made it quite clear that she
她不想我们插手
wants us OFF her case.
她说明天会和我们谈的，只要她准备好了
So,uh,she said she'd talk to us tomorrow. When she's ready.
Tamsin在休息恢复当中，所以我决定这周末出来玩
Tamsin's resting, recovering. So I packed a weekend bag.
我们就给Bo一点私人空间吧
Holla,we're gonna give Bo some elbow room.
我们怎么能相信他
How do we trust him?
我们不能，你以为我想这样吗
We don't.And believe me,I am not happy about this either.
你知道的，新男人出现，妹子就见色忘友了
You know new guy comes along,girl drops her friends.
真是他娘的不爽
Classic suckage.
但我们相信下我们的妹子好吗，尊重她的选择
But we gotta trust our girl.Respect Bo's decision.
我很高兴你们能帮我
I'm so glad you guys could help.
拿杯咖啡吧，别客气
Grab a coffee, don't be shy.
Bo
Bo?
你没事吧
Is everything okay?
我要想想清楚
I need to understand.
这要是个错误怎么办
What if this was a mistake?
我想相信你 真的
I want to trust you, I do...
我从未想过我会再次回到这个物理平面上
I never imagined I'd be on this physical plane again.
我为了要救你 自愿回到了火车上
I had to go back to the train willingly to save you.
我这么做了
And I did.
为了你我成了黑暗派  我化不可能为可能
I went dark for you. I did the impossible.
可这 我们刚做的事
But this. What we did...
也是必须的
Was just as necessary.
Kenzi Dyson Lauren Trick  对不起 他们
Kenzi, Dyson, Lauren, Trick. I'm sorry, they...
只是需要一些时间 我也是
Just need time. And so do I.
你说了我们一旦想起来 你就会告诉他们
You said once we remembered,  you would talk to them.
我知道 但还不到时候
I know. But not yet.
回忆回来了 感情也是
The memories are back, the feelings.
但现在我们在这 在真实世界里一起
But now that we're here, in the real world together,
在我的世界里
in my world...
我要弄明白 真的弄清楚
I need to understand. Really understand.
你骚扰我朋友 跟踪我 绑架我
You have harassed my friends. Stalked and kidnapped me.
还把老娘最爱的酒吧炸掉了
And you just blew up my favorite pub.
我们就算算这笔账吧流浪者
So let's get to it... Wanderer.
我的心你别暴躁
Be still my heart...
又一个黑毛
another brunette.
我特么烦死这歌了
I am so sick of this song.
你到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
嘿 我跟你说话呢
Hey, I'm talking to you.
我在黑烟里一路过来
I came all this way via black smoke,
你总得给我个说法
I think I deserve an explanation.
亲你有以下两个选择
Well sweetheart,you got two choices.
一，你留下来，我假装和你谈恋爱
One. You can stay, I can pretend to court you,
谈烦了就把你送走
get bored with you and send you away.
二，你下站就可以下车
Two, you can get off at the next stop.
不管选哪个 你都不会记得
Either way you'll forget everything.
还有选择三
Here's option three.
你告诉我你为什么绑架我
You tell me why you kidnapped me.
我不知道你为什么在这 真的
I don't know why you are here. Seriously, I don't.
下个问题
Next question?
为什么费了这么大劲把我弄来 又要把我送走
Why go through all of this trouble just to send me away?
你要想打一架 或者斗个智  或者
If you wanted some epic fight,some battle of wits, some...
来点罗曼史 那你上错火车了
sweeping romance, you're on the wrong train.
这什么也没有 快走吧
Nothing to see here. Move it along.
侍女
Handmaiden.
把
Take uh...
Bo 我叫Bo
Bo. My name is Bo.
带Bo去她房间  她下站就下车
Take Bo to her chambers, she'll be getting off at the next stop,
要是她为了自己好
if she knows what's good for her.
不了谢谢
No thanks.
你的味道很淡 但你是异种
Your scent is faint but you are Fae.
小精灵的孤儿 在人类世界里由人类抚养长大
Orphaned pixie. Raised by humans, in the human world.
*Pixie 民间传说中的小精灵 通常淘气又活泼 爱搞无伤大雅的恶作剧*
好像已经不能更糟了 结果现在又来个这
As if that wasn't already random enough, now this.
很不方便
It's very inconvenient.
你可以这么说
That's one way to put it.
游泳池只能专人进出
Well exclusive access to the corporate pool
说明是内部人员干的
would indicate an inside job.
你们这在研究什么地下黑科技吗
Is there any sort of suspicious research going on?
我拿到个产品 要市场化
I'm handed a product and I market it.
这产品怎么造出来的倒是个谜
How it's actually made is a mystery.
你们应该去问Darren Clare
Darren Clare would be your guy.
他是产品开发部的老大
He's the head of Product Development.
是个谜一般的男纸
Now there's a man with secrets.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. I really appreciate this.
我喜欢你的塔希提日落指甲油
And I appreciate your Tahiti Sunset manicure.
我自己倒是偏向塔希提日出
I'm a Tahiti Sunrise girl,myself.
视觉敏锐啊
Sharp eye.
我们是最棒的
Hm. You hired the best.
来吧 我们来企业化
Now kids. Let's get corporate.
脏兮兮的微波炉 动手动脚的经理 滴漏咖啡
We got saucy microwaves. Grabby managers. Drip coffee.
我们怎么干
How we doin' this?
我建立了两个临时的企业文件
Actually I've set up two temp corporate profiles.
好吧 我看就我和Kenzi来卧底吧
Okay well how about Kenzi and I take the field.
我在训练她
I've been training her.
火影偷者  看看你的内裤
As a shadow thief. Check your panties.
有人丢了内裤吗
Anyone missing any panties?
你表再酱紫了好吗
You have got to stop doing that.
这可不是我教的
I did not teach her to do that.
Kenzi 我觉得你当个
Kenzi, I think you'll fit in just fine
邮差兼修理工会天衣无缝
as mail distribution and maintenance.
不干 接着说
Offended. Moving on.
Dyson 你就当个效率顾问
Dyson, you'll go in as Efficiency Consultant.
听着  这栋楼装着最新的
Now listen, this building is rigged with the latest
热感应保安系统
heat sensor security.
你俩要是慌里慌张
If either one of you gets flustered or nervous,
系统就会知道
big brother is alerted.
我已经把你俩都黑进了热签名系统
I have managed to hack you into the heat signature system.
你俩可以检测你们自己或者别的嫌疑犯
So you can monitor yourselves or any suspects.
务必处处提防 保持冷静
Just remember to stay alert, calm,
更重要的是 融入
most importantly, blend in.
你信不信Diana把我们的角色搞错了
Can you believe Diana got our roles wrong?
惊讶
Shocking.
干嘛  我从来没穿过套装啊
What,I never get to wear a suit.
这是你的邮件 白领小妹
Here's your mail workin' girl.
那是什么
What is that noise?
我正在消灭一些可能有害的细菌
Sorry I was eliminating some potentially harmful bacteria.
大肠杆菌 沙门氏菌之类的
You know, E. coli, enteritis salmonella that kind of thing.
你看见什么了吗 发生了什么事
Sorry. What do you see? What's happening?
我们在个酸奶广告里
Well,we're basically in a yogurt commercial.
热能监视器正常工作中吗
How's the heat monitor working?
看来我是热翻天的那位
Um...looks like I'm the hottest one around.
我喜欢这个装备
I like this gadget!
你很热是因为你很兴奋 肯子
You're hot 'cause you're excited Kenz,
冷静 否则警报器就要响了
you gotta stay calm or you're gonna alert security.
好吧 给Darren Clare送信
Okay,delivering mail to Darren Clare.
你原地待命
Standby.
不可以
I don't think so.
不许任何人直接给Clare先生送东西
No one delivers anything 'directly' to Mr.Clare.
我也不行
Not even me.
那就是说有特别的信箱了
Why,is there some sort of secret mail slot or something?
是的
Yes.
哎呀手滑了
Oh how clumsy of me.
你在大企业工作怎么蓬头垢面的
Aren't you a little unkempt for a corporate setting?
你发音这么不清还接电话呢
Aren't you a little nasal to be answering phones?
我没
I am not...
噢
Ouch!
Dyson得一分
Dyson: one. Man Drescher: zero.
热能贴到位了
Heat band-aid secured.
你确定这能行
Are you sure this is gonna work?
肯定的 已经在工作了
Ah, yes. It's registering!
Kenzi
Kenzi?
邮件在路上了
Mail is on the move.
真不幸  老娘被盯梢啊
Unfortunately, I'm being stalked like a celebrity
就跟名人在候父子停车场一般
at a Whole Foods parking lot.
*Whole Foods 连锁超市*
你要进入通风管道里
You need to get into that vent system
在我们失去热能跟踪前跟着那邮件
to track that mail before we lose heat.
好 我来引开守卫
Okay, I'm gonna distract the guard.
我用我表哥Dimitri给的相机兼投影仪
I'll record myself on a camera that cousin Dimitri provided
给自己录个相
that also doubles as a projector.
再在桌子前放个屏幕
I'll install a screen in front of my desk...
我觉得吉普赛科技还是就算了吧
Yeah, I don't think we should be trusting Gypsy technology.
就等我 等我20分钟吧
Just give me, uh, give me 20.
那也行
Or we could just do that.
不用谢
You're welcome.
好了 进入通风管道
Okay, I am getting my vent on.
要是像异型那电影一样
If this goes Aliens,
老娘就要化身Sigourney Weaver杀出去
I am Sigourney Weavering outta there.
*Sigourney Weaver 异型电影的主演*
噢
Eugh!
肯子
Kenz?
没那么严重啦  我保证
That was way more graceful than it sounded, I swear.
Kenzi 你看到啥了吗
Kenzi. Do you have a visual?
腿
Legs.
白花花的腿
Lots and lots of legs.
又长
Long
又苗条，雕塑般的小腿
lean,sculpted calves.
看来他们天天勤做下蹲运动
Looks like someone never missed squat day.
有人来了
Someone's here.
警报解除 没人来
Okay,false alarm. No one's here.
只是Darren的邮件
It's just Darren's mail.
好多邮件
A lot of mail.
让我来看看
Okay,what do we got here?
有Chez Lounge的订阅信
We got a subscription to Chez Lounge.
哦看这
Oh hello.
Tad的医疗账单
Medical bills for Tad.
好几十万啊 还很多
We're talking like six figures. And a lot of them.
Darren的助理  他得什么病了
Darren's assistant? What's he being treated for?
恩 动脉什么什么的 我不知道
Uh...Perry-foral somethin'-somethin', I dunno.
我照个照片发给你好了
Why don't I just take a picture and send it to you.
狼叔你怎么样
How you doing,D?
Lauren我给你发了点东西
Lauren I'm sending you some visuals to scan.
我正看这呢
Yeah,I'm looking at them.
那个植物 你得给我拿一株来
That plant. I need you to bring me one.
很罕见 似乎是水生的
It's unusual and possibly aquatic.
给我最爱的医生的花
Flowers for my favourite doctor.
马上就来
Coming up.
好了 两个前任打情骂俏
Okay! Playful banter between duelling exes?!
这池子里都是海水
It's a salt water pool.
过滤系统里我找到个珍珠
I found a pearl in the filtration system.
好我宣布这是我的
Ooh! I'm calling dibs.
要不是证据就归我了
If it's not evidence I want it.
我是不是打扰你了
Am I interrupting?
确实没错
Frankly, yes.
天啊你在出汗
Oh my, you're sweating.
我一想要全副武装收拾女仆就会这样
That's what happens when I gear up to kick handmaiden ass.
你不把我送下火车 我就要这么干
Which I will do if you don't help me off this train.
下一站还得三天呢
Next stop's not for three days.
你现在跳下去就会蒸发掉
If you jump before then, you'll evaporate.
火车停车你不跟个元素精灵下去的话
Leave when it's stopped without an elemental,
会得穿越平面的病 会死掉
and you'll get transcendental sickness and die.
现在 我们来打扮下你吧
Now. Shall we freshen you up?
你的号码
In your size...
你会很漂亮的
you'll look ravishing.
我才不想为了一个绑架我的人
I'm not really into looking ravishing
精心打扮
for someone who kidnapped me.
哦 快别这么想
Oh,please stop looking at it that way.
那还能怎么想
There's no other way to see it!
他要不是那么悲剧
If he wasn't so pathetic.
我都把他扔下火车了
I would have thrown him off his own train.
我知道可能看起来不这样 但是
I know it might not seem like it on the surface but,
他是个很好的人
he is a great man.
给他个机会好吗
Give him a chance.
也给我们一个机会
Give us all a chance.
信不信由你  我们需要你
Believe it or not? We need you.
和流浪者共进晚餐
Dinner? With the Wanderer?
他叫Rainer
His name is Rainer.
你看上去也饿坏了
And you do look hungry.
你干嘛没在你黑暗派那边
Then why aren't you doing this from the comfort
安全的做这事
of your new Dark digs?
我想来这和你们一起啊 更接近现场
I wanted to be here with you guys, close to all the action.
Bo给你打电话了吗 泳池帅哥
Has Bo called? Pool boy.
还没呢
Not yet, no.
肯子
Kenz?
还没  但她会打的
Not yet, but she will.
要像George Michael那样信仰 信仰 信仰啊啊啊啊
We gotta have George Michael faith-a, faith-a, faith-ahhh.
*George Michael 80年代著名歌手 faith是他的一首歌*
这不是珍珠 是结块的盐结晶
It's not a pearl... it's a crystallized salt deposit.
你刚说是结块的盐结晶
Did you just say crystallized salt deposit?
我这句子还能有什么双重含义不成
Can that sentence be mistaken for some other sentence?
特么的
Dammit!
怎么了 发生什么事了
Why, what's going on?
我们不该插手这案子的
We should never have taken this case.
Kenzi 你得赶快出来
Kenzi, you need to get out.
可我们还没破案呢
But we haven't solved it yet!
无所谓 赶紧走 你懂了吗
Doesn't matter, get out. Do you copy?
Dyson 到底怎么回事
What is it Dyson?
食人者
A flesh eater?
鲨鱼龙卷风
Sharknado?
比那更糟
Worse.
是人鱼
Mermaids.
人鱼
我被炒了
Fired?
一年给你8万刀就是让你在烤面包机旁边八卦的
Eighty thousand dollars a year to gossip by a toaster oven?
没错 你被解雇了
Yeah. Fired.
但是
But...
住嘴
Uh, zip. Zip.
天啊人鱼 我爱死她们了
Oh my God Mermaids? I love mermaids!
我是说爱到要死
But like, LOVE them.
肯子 他们是海里的神经病
They are the psychopaths of the sea Kenz.
隔海有眼  是他们的座右铭
"The Seas Have Eyes" is their cultural motto.
*来自著名恐怖电影隔山有眼<The Hills Have Eyes> 讲普通人被变异人围攻折磨的故事*
我这辈子做梦都想着
I have lied awake at night my entire life
这人鱼的一天 我能遇到
thinking of the marvellous mer-day when I would meet
一个用鳍拍水 贝壳做胸衣 像Daryl Hannah那样的
a fin-flapping, sea-shell-bra wearing, Daryl Hannah…
*Daryl Hannah 著名演员 曾演金发美人鱼*
哦我滴娘啊
Oh my God.
他们是稀有又神奇的物种
They are a rare and fascinating species.
是啊她们用叉子梳头
Yeah. They comb their hair with forks!
对 在他们用叉子戳完你脸之后
Yeah, right after they stab your face with them.
在他们把你去往新世界的
Just before they blow up your ship
船弄沉之前
that's en route to the new world.
可她们会和螃蟹唱二重唱对吧
Yeah but then they sing duets with crabs?
醒醒  肯子 醒醒
No, they don't, Kenz.
这不是儿童电影
This is not a children's movie.
好吧  他们要是真的这么坏
Okay fine. But if they're that bad, don't we think the good
Alaria的好人们不该远离他们吗
people of Alaria deserve the chance to be mermaid-free?
她说的没错
She's right.
好吧 但是我们得小心 他们神出鬼没
Fine, but we have to be careful. They could be anywhere.
你的女仆喜欢做媒
Your Handmaiden likes playing matchmaker.
她一般来说干得挺好
She's usually better at it.
其他对象至少能穿个好看的衣服
Other dates bothered to dress up.
进入童话角色
Play into the fairy tale.
但你看上去就像是来刺杀我的一样
Whereas you look like you're here to assassinate me.
我对完美结局没有兴趣
I am not looking for happily ever after.
我家就是完美结局 有我的家人和朋友
I have that at home. With my family, my friends.
你知道 你逼我离开了他们
You know, the people you stole me from.
可喜可贺 但是再说一次 我没绑你
Congratulations. But again,I didn't bring you here.
这个有配酱料吗
Is there sauce for this?
Rainer 你到底想怎么样
What do you want with me Rainer?
女仆把我的名字告诉你了
The handmaiden told you my name.
是的 余下的真相由你来说
Yeah, and now you're gonna tell me everything else.
啊
Agh.
你以为你一来就可以对我呼来喝去
You think you can come in here and push me around.
表现得很强硬 要求答案
Act tough. Demand answers...
你不告诉我答案我就烦死你
I keep barking until I get answers.
你改变不了什么的
You are not going to change anything.
你是个淫妖对吗
Are you a Succubus?
这些日子黑暗异种都吃什么呢
Tell me what do the Dark Fae devour these days?
我怎么知道 我又没结盟
I wouldn't know. I'm unaligned.
这不可能
That's impossible.
你是说像这开在茫茫虚无之中的火车
Impossible like a magical train that travels through other
跳车就会挂掉那样不可能吗
dimensions and kills you when you try to leave it.
我真希望这有陪酱料
I really wish there was sauce...
你是什么异种
What kind of Fae are you?
记忆消除者吗
Huh? Some memory wiper?
我操纵不了记忆
Memory is not my power.
那是什么
What is it,then?
是我的诅咒
My curse.
什么诅咒
What curse?
人人都有负担不是吗
We all have our burdens.
没错 可你的把我烦透了 流浪者
True. But yours happens to be a pain in my ass, Wanderer.
Rainer
Rainer.
请叫我Rainer
Please, call me Rainer.
我管你是谁 我回房间吃我的晚饭
Whoever you are? I'll be taking my dinner to go.
对Tad进行效率评估
Approaching Tad for Efficiency Evaluation.
情报马上就来 没错 姐就是这么牛x
Intel imminent because, yes, I AM that good.
我是KLD咨询公司的Lorna Larson
Hi, I'm Lorna Larson from KLD Consulting.
*KLD Kenzi+Lauren+Dyson*
我是来评估你的职位的效率的
Here to evaluate the efficiency of your position.
我们是不是 去走走
Why don't we uh, take a walk.
或者滚滚 要不还是就在这吧
Or a roll, or we can just hang out. Here.
我是这公司里最有效率的人了
I'm the most efficient person at Alaria.
为了效率起见我们长话短说
And in the spirit of efficiency, let's make this quick.
好吧  你的残疾影响你工作吗
Right. Does your disability ever affect your work?
你的脑子是不是进了洗发水
Does your leave-in shampoo seep into your scalp
被烧坏了
and affect yours?
登登登登
Zing-a-ling-a-ding-dong!
你不是助理  你是猪理
You're not an assistant, you're a SASS-istant.
我的职位描述里有
It's in the job description.
好吧  你的腿到底是怎么会事
So uh, what happened to your legs? Or lack thereof.
你有小提琴和十秒钟吗
Do you have ten seconds and a violin?
是的
Yeah!
大四的时候
Fourth year college.
我得了末梢动脉梗阻的病
I got sick with peripheral arterial disease.
要不截肢 要不就得死
It was either amputate or die.
天价医疗账单 父母又失业 爽啊
Piling medical bills,laid off parents. Fun.
然后Darren出现了
Then, Darren came along.
给了我工作 还帮我付账
Covered our expenses. Gave me a job.
他救了我的命
He saved my life.
现在 保护他是我的任务
And now it's my mission to protect him.
我要保证没有任何人任何事伤害到他
Make sure nothing, or no one, ever gets in his way.
如果他 曾经做过 不和谐的事情
So if he, um, ever did anything, un-kosher,
你还会保护他吗
would you cover for him?
Darren是个学霸
Darren's a genius.
大家都想等着看他失败的笑话
People would love to see him fall.
我会让这些疯子离他远远的
I protect him from the crazies.
我要开会了
I have a meeting to attend.
因为我就是那么有效率
Because I'm efficient that way.
没错
Right.
Tad不是美人鱼  重复 不是美人鱼
Tad is not a mermaid. Repeat, not a mermaid.
他似乎一提Darren Clare就变得很自我防卫
He sure got defensive about Darren Clare.
哦你好
Oh hello.
你偷的那些文件 这种肢解方式
Those files you stole... these dismemberments
是由精确的手术做出来的
were executed with surgical precision.
不是Diana遇到的那种游泳池大腿小偷
Not like the pool hack job that Diana suffered?
你找到匹配了吗
Do you see a match?
这些都是男人的腿
All of these belonged to men.
那为什么忽然砍起女人的腿了
Why the sudden interest in women's parts?
Kenzi如果你可以给我一点样品 或者
Kenzi. If you could get me a sample or a...
收到 我再回去一次
Got it. I'm going back in.
也许这次我可以看见美人鱼
And maybe this time I'll see a mermaid.
随便 您请进吧
By all means,let yourself in.
谁在乎隐私呢
Who needs privacy?
噢
Oh.
至少弹点开心的吧
At least play something more cheerful.
末日倒数？你不是吧？
Final Countdown? Really?
*Final Countdown  瑞典80年代乐队Europe的代表作*
你玩战国风云？
You play Risk?
*Risk：由孩之宝旗下的Parker Brothers发行是一种图版游戏上的战棋*
我很早前输了
I lost a long time ago.
我的直觉告诉我你不是在指游戏
Something tells me you're not talking about a game.
不
No.
你问我我的力量是什么
You asked me what my power was.
我以前有预知能力
I used to have foresight.
在战场中
In battle.
我可以预先看见我的敌人的攻击
I was able to see my opponent's attacks before they happened.
我善用了我的力量 结束了光明和黑暗之间的战争
I put it to good use, fought to end Light and Dark.
你怎么做到的
How would you do that?
我看到好人在所谓的正义名义下
I've seen good people slaughtered in the name
被屠杀
of what is supposedly "right".
家庭分裂 他们被迫划清界限
Family's torn apart,  forced to choose a side.
互相争斗 而不是相互扶持
Fighting against each other instead of with one another.
暴政崛起
A tyrannical rule was on the rise.
谁的暴政
Who's rule?
我不能
I can't re...
我不能够 对不起
I can't, I'm sorry.
我不记得为什么我会在这里
Not being able to remember why I'm here.
谁诅咒了我 谁拿走了我的力量 为什么会发生这一切
Who cursed me. who took my power away. What this is all for.
这是
It's, it's...
这是一种折磨
It's torture.
人可以学会身无长物的存活
One can learn to live with Or without... almost anything.
这不是活着
That's not living.
下一站 和上站一样
Next stop, same as the last.
上一站 和下站一样
Last stop, same before next.
来吧小键盘 解锁
Come on keypad, work with me.
有人靠近了 但是他们的温度签名是蓝色的
Someone's approaching but their heat signature's blue.
什么意思
What does that mean?
颜色代表温度
Colours correspond to temperature.
这位很冷 和黄瓜一样冷
Well this one's cool. Cool as a cucumber.
或者和鱼一样冷 ,Kenzi出去
Or cold as a fish, Kenzi get out.
爬大厦楼梯是一码事
Climbing the corporate ladder is one thing.
爬大厦的排气口 你就死定了
But crawling through the corporate vent? Is a dead end.
所以 你不但偷了我的腿 还想偷我的邮件
So, not only are you stealing my legs, you're stealing my mail?
你从哪拿到这些邮件的
Where'd you get these letters?
男人鱼 我得说 我有点失望啊
Merman? I gotta say, I'm a little disappointed.
你从哪拿到这些的
Where did you get these?
你的助手
Your assistant.
Tad从来没把它们给我
Tad never gave them to me.
他肯定以为她是个跟踪狂
He must have thought she was a stalker.
谁
Who?
我的姐妹
My sister.
这里有超过一打的珍珠
There's over a dozen pearls here.
你知道这意味着什么吗
Do you know what this means?
她喜欢星期二爽歪歪
She loves buck-a-shuck Tuesdays?
她会杀了我的
She's gonna kill me.
也许这是你偷Diana的腿的惩罚
Well maybe you deserve it for stealing Diana's legs.
Diana丢了腿吗 我听说她请了病假
Diana lost her legs?! I heard she took a leave of absence.
你是说你的姐姐干了这事
Are you saying your sister did it?
我很确定
Pretty sure.
但是她不知道怎么装上去
But she doesn't know how to attach them.
你从哪里拿到你的
Where'd you get yours?
Tad生病后他成为了我的第一捐献人
When Tad got sick, he became my first donor.
我的团队从干细胞中发展了一种组织融合系统
My team developed a tissue fusion system using stem cells.
听着 我在这不安全  Dominique快来了
Look, I'm not safe here. Dominique is close.
请帮帮我 把我带到Diana那里去
Please help me. Take me to Diana.
我怎么能相信你
How can I trust you?
我站在满屋男人的性感大腿中
I am standing in a room full of man gams.
你签了你的捐献人卡片吗
Did you sign your donor card?
他们都是自愿的我没有伤害任何人
They were all willing.I didn't hurt anyone.
我这辈子 一直渴望融入进我不属于的
My entire life, I wanted to be a part of a world
世界中
I didn't belong to.
这是我唯一的办法了
This is my only way.
你想要和大家在一起
You wanna be where the people are.
我的神 Diana的腿
Tahiti Sunset. Diana's legs.
她比我想像的还要近 我要死了
She's closer than I thought. I'm dead.
不我会带你离开这里的
No, I can get you out of here.
她会找寻更多的腿 不是吗
She'll be looking for more legs, won't she?
对 她可以藏在泳池的水循环系统里
Yeah. She can hide in the pool water system.
你得把她钓出来
You're gonna have to fish her out.
我知道最好的鱼铒
I know the best bait in town.
表现的自然点 去游个小泳
Just act natural. Go for a swim.
你去给我游
You go for a swim.
现在
Now!
两分钟提示 下站两分钟后到达
Two minute warning. Next station in two minutes.
你怎么做到的
What did you do?
在我七岁的时候
When I was seven, I...
是 你
It is. You.
你要错过下车了
You're going to miss your stop.
但这个 我们
But this. Us.
走吧 趁你还来得及
Go. While you still can.
不
No.
走 快走
Go. GO!
啊啊啊啊啊
AAAHHHHGGGGGHH!!
我在做什么
What am I doing?
不喜欢刚才的水下频率 是吧
Didn't like that underwater frequency, did ya?
天啊 她好美
God. She's beautiful.
腿
Legs!
对  那确实叫腿
Yes, that's what they're called.
腿
Legs!
不是你的
Not yours.
是Lauren的 这是有区别的哦
Lauren's. There's a difference.
混蛋美人鱼  我应该现在就干掉她
God damn mermaids. I should just end her now, right?
你想来点寿司吗
You feel like some sushi?
不 我要走路
NO! I need to walk.
腿
Legs.
你伤害了别人 这样不对
You are hurting people. It's wrong.
我没有 我需要腿 才能去找我弟弟
I didn't. I need them to get to my brother.
他离家出走的时候 把我抛弃了
He abandoned me when he left home for his "Walking".
那是啥
What's that?
和阿米什人的青春期一样吗？
Like a Rumspringa?
当阿米什人离开他们的家一段时间
When the Amish community leave their home for a while
*Amish:基督新教再洗礼派，以拒绝汽车及电力等现代设施，过著简朴的与世隔绝的生活而闻名。*
去探索世界 然后决定继续在外飘
to explore the world,then the decide whether
或者回家 过上传统的生活
or not to come back, live a traditional life.
我们可以获得一年的魔腿在地上行走
We get magic legs for a year to walk the earth.
我出去了又乖乖回到家
I had my time. Came home like a good girl.
但Darren不知怎么的居然可以永远走路
But Darren somehow made his Walking permanent.
而当你发现你遵循传统  却毫无意义
And you thought you'd follow suit, only without the means.
你知道被忽略的感觉是什么吗
Do you have any idea what it feels like to be ignored?
被你所爱的人拒之门外
To be locked out by someone that you love?
我把这些珍珠寄给Darren
I've been sending these pearls to Darren.
这是第十八个 意味着我受够了
That's my eighteenth. It means I've suffered enough
我要杀人
to take someone's life.
那你是来这里杀你的兄弟吗
So you're here to kill your own brother?
我绝对不会这么做
I would never.
而我的姐姐
My sister on the other hand.
她发誓会把Darren带回去
She promised to get Darren and come back.
我等待啊等待
I waited, and waited.
等了好多年
For years.
她欺骗了我
She lied to me.
所以我拿走了她的人腿
So I took her human walking sticks.
你的姐姐
Your sister...?
所以也不是你
So it wasn't you.
我以为你是想要把我赶出公司
Thought you were trying to cut me out of my position.
用割掉你的腿的方式
By cutting off your legs?
男人鱼不都这么干吗
Isn't that what mermen do?
我希望你们喜欢吞拿鱼
I hope you guys like tuna!
海洋之音
Ocean speak!
你必须教我点牛逼的美人鱼脏话
You've gotta teach me some epic mer-swears?
这里
Here.
艾马你要披肩吗 你好冷啊
Oi vay! Do you need a pashmina? You're freezing cold!
和鱼一样冷
Cold as a... fish?
你不是小精灵 你是美人鱼
You're not pixie, you're a mermaid.
你是我的新下半身
And you're my new bottom half.
我不懂
I don't get it,
你要知道是你哥哥干的 为什么要雇佣我们
why would you hire us if you thought your own brother did it?
我以为他想除掉我
I thought he was trying to get rid of me.
所以我让你们来扮演侦探的角色除掉他
So I hired you to play detective to get rid of him.
对一个没有菊花的种族来说 你倒挺菊花残的
For a species without assholes, you sure act like ones.
*assholes：有菊花和混蛋的双意*
放下武器
Drop the knife.
再走一步 她就成鱼饵了
Take one more step and she's chum.
Dominique  Dominique  Dominique
Dominique, Dominique, Dominique.
老把事情搞砸
Always screwing everything up.
我想你们两个人都回家
I want you both to come home
她是我们脑残妹妹
She's our sloppy sister.
啊
Aigt!
Dyson
Dyson.
Dominique 你真是眼界狭窄
Dominique, you are so small pond.
Darren和我为了腿付出多少努力你知道吗
Darren and I worked hard for our legs!
我们回家去
Let's just all go back home.
你们答应过我会回来的
You promised me that you would come back...
你们把我忘了
you forgot about me.
Dominique
Dominique.
你和我们一起在这呆着
You stay here with us.
会很完美的
It's perfect...
医生的腿归你
you get the doctor's.
这个扭来扭去的东西的腿归Diana
Diana gets the squirmy one's.
我则用狼腿升级
And I upgrade to wolf legs.
Dominique别听他的
Dominique, don't listen.
你必须帮我们
You have to help us.
不
No.
我喜欢他的主意
I like his idea!
停下来 你快杀死他了
Stop it, you're killing him!
看看
Look at that.
团队精神
Teamwork.
一家团聚啊
The family's back together!
我们会拿到我们的腿
We'll get our legs.
把Alaria科技炸掉
Blow up Alaria Tech.
去茂伊岛重新开始
Start over again in Maui.
*Maui：夏威夷第二大岛*
是时候让我们的种族崛起了
Now's the time for our kind to rise.
向海壳们说再见
Goodbye sea shells.
向维多利亚的秘密招手
Hello Victoria Secret!
*Victoria Secret：内衣品牌 你懂的*
没有什么能够阻挡我们
There's nothing that can stop us.
除了自来水
Except tap water.
尼玛
Oh shit.
你错过了上次停车
And you missed the last stop.
上上站
And the one before that.
上上上上上上上上站
And the one before that.And the one before that...
这地方的时间很不同
Time is different in this place.
我的朋友们还安全吗
Are my friends still safe?
Kenzi和 Dyson快找到指南针了
Kenzi and Dyson are coming close to finding the compass.
当他们把它打碎 他们就会记起你
When they break it, they'll remember you.
而你将忘记我
And you won't remember me.
这很值得
It was worth it.
即使我将再不见到你
Even if I never see you again.
毕竟 这是我的诅咒
After all, it is my curse.
去你的诅咒
Screw your curse.
万事具备
Everything's ready.
没人回去过
Nobody's ever come back...
再说一次
Tell me again.
所有的线索都有了
All the clues are in place.
等我回到家
When I return home.
它们会把我带回你身边 即使我不记得
They'll guide me back to you, even though I won't remember.
当你的乌鸦们把那个漂亮的歌手带来
When your crows brought us that gorgeous singer
为我们表演 我告诉她来找我
to perform for us, I told her to come find me...
谁 谁告诉你来的
Who? Who told you to come?
你
You did.
接着是Hugin
And then there's Hugin.
当我把瓶子打开 他会把我带回来
When I open that jar, he will guide me back...
如果这还不够
And if that is not enough,
有一件事绝对可以
there is one thing that I know for sure will work...
和黑暗派签约
A contract with the dark.
做我的见证人
Be my witness?
不
No.
这违背你的本性 违背我为之而战的所有东西
It betrays who you are. Everything I fought for.
这不会长久的
This is never gonna stick.
我唯一知道的
If there is one thing that I know
我绝对不会和任何一派结盟
I would never in a million years align myself.
当我回到家 发现我成为了黑暗派
If I go home, and find out that I am dark...
我一定会赴汤蹈火的找出理由来
I will move heaven and earth to find out how that happened.
把我带回你身边
Bringing me back to you.
当我回来时 我会摧毁这份契约
When I return, I will destroy this contract.
把你从火车中救出来
Save you from this train.
我会帮你赢回一切
I will get you everything back.
你的记忆
Your memory.
你的力量
Your power.
如果我是怪物呢
What if I'm a monster?
那怎么办
What then?
那么我会亲手杀掉你
Then I'll kill you myself.
现在 你只用让这个火车继续前进
For now, all you have to do is keep this train running.
好吗
Okay?
活下去
Stay alive.
吾乘光来
Unanimes venit lumen.
久安入人之思
Unanimes veniat pax.
祸也
Malum est...
太好了 你们都在这里
Oh good, you're all here.
还是这么诡异
Being creepy.
你又违法了 淫妖
You have broken our laws again, Succubus.
流浪者不属于这个世界
The Wanderer is not intended for this physical plane.
那是他的诅咒
It is his curse.
老娘就擅长破除诅咒
Breaking curses is kind of my thing.
Rainer 趁现在
Rainer, now!
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
我可以预见他们的攻击
I can see their attacks.
我预知的能力又回来了 Bo 我们有危险了
My power of foresight is back, Bo. And we're in danger.
这就是你被诅咒的原因
This is the reason you were cursed.
对反叛军来说这个力量太大了
This is too much power for a rebel.
你腐朽的委员会促成了反叛军
Your corrupt council warrants a rebellion.
你说的话是在亵渎神明
What you speak is blasphemy.
为了惩罚你的罪过 我们要杀死你认领的人类
For your crime, we will kill your claimed human.
还有那医生
The doctor.
狼
The wolf.
和海妖
The siren.
你爱的所有人都会被毁灭
Everyone you love will perish.
当你见证他们的毁灭之后 我们会再杀掉你
After you have witnessed their destruction... we will kill you.
捉住淫妖和战士
Capture the Succubus and The Warrior.
找到她的朋友 家人
Seek out her friends, her families.
我们要她目睹他们身受折磨
We will make her watch as they suffer.
我不想接下来的事情发生
I don't want what comes next.
你不想接下来的事情发生
You don't want what comes next.
你知道你 打败不了我们的 淫妖
You know you can't defeat us, Succubus.
她没说错
She's right.
上次我吸他们的气  差点被反杀
Last time I succubused them, it almost killed me.
他们可以反弹我的攻击
They'll reflect my attacks because it uses my power.
守护者和闪电一样快
The Keeper is quick as lightning.
但是在我的帮助下你可以成功
But you can do this with my help.
怎么做
How?
躲闪
Duck.
啥
What?
躲避
Duck!
阻挡
Block!
踢
Kick!
神仙姐姐王语嫣啊
Holy shit.
居然有用
It's working.
接下来干什么
What next?
你相信我吗
Do you trust me?
一旦我们把这些海绵摆脱
Once we get rid of this sea foam,
他们在下水道系统里就无法生存了
it's unlikely they'll survive the sewage system.
你怎么知道会杀死他们的呢
How'd you know it would kill them anyway?
*请观赏<下水道的美人鱼>*
我注意到自来水会杀死水族馆的植物
I noticed tap water killed the aquatic plant.
Diana 滴水不进
Diana refusing to drink a drop combined
外加Dominique的珍珠的成分
with the composition of Dominique's pearl.
海水池
Salt water pool.
剩下就是反渗透的事了
The rest was osmosis!
哈
Huh!
聪明
Smarty pants.
你知道吗
You know what?
我们合作天下无敌
We make an excellent team.
确实
We do.
Bo没联系我们
Bo never called.
Kenzi
Kenzi.
我担心她
No, I'm worried about her...
我是说
I mean...
他们到底在干什么
What are they even doing?!
Bo
Bo...
下一步是啥
What's next?
你干得了
You got this.
淫妖
Succubus.
你要是听了他的话
If you do this, if you follow him...
你的命运会比最可怕的噩梦还要恐怖
you will suffer a fate beyond your worst nightmares.
比你那淫荡的母亲还要可怕的命运
A fate even worse than your own whore of a mother's!
你会被拖入地狱底层
You will be dragged beneath irkalla,
像被诅咒的邪恶之子一般
damned like the spawn of evil that you are!!!
再也没有威胁
No more threats.
再也没有议会了
No more councils.
噢
Eugh!
贱人
Bitch.
Bo
Bo...
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
走开
Leave.
这不能等
This can't wait.
你还敢来我家
How dare you come into my home?
我的房间
Into my room?
Rainer会让你杀掉Una Mens
Rainer will ask you to slay the Una Mens.
我知道他们没干好事
I know that they've wronged us.
他们是坏人
That they're evil.
我求你了
But I am begging you:
别去干
Don't do it.
他们的能力就会注入到一颗种子里
Their power will be amassed into the single remaining seed.
什么种子
What seed?
起源之种
The Origin Seed.
从我这被偷走的那个
It was stolen from me.
被不该持有的人拿到了
In the wrong hands...
怎么了Trick
What, Trick?
你要向我保证
Just give me your word.
我就这点要求
That's all I ask.